<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>pants-hub - yap</title>
    <subtitle>Lucas Newcomb&#x27;s personal site</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://pants721.github.io/tags/yap/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://pants721.github.io"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2024-11-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://pants721.github.io/tags/yap/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>on death</title>
        <published>2024-11-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-11-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Lucas Newcomb
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://pants721.github.io/blog/grace/"/>
        <id>https://pants721.github.io/blog/grace/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://pants721.github.io/blog/grace/">&lt;p&gt;i dont think ill ever fully understand it.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
ive spent my nights twisting and turning over how &lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
one moment you&#x27;re there and the next you&#x27;re just not. &lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
the sheets are all hot and horrible now and still understanding alludes me.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;how wrong this is. to leave no mark in the sand, no note on the fridge, no reason why.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
maybe a fool would see the long trail of sand that had been drudged through for years and scratch his head at it&#x27;s end.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
maybe i&#x27;ve been made a fool.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
death makes what it wants of me.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
my notebook of coping strategies and meditations does me no good in the face of the great equalizer.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
its very loud at first. it comes at you screaming and kicking; crying &amp;quot;how could it be&amp;quot;.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
shock subsides.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
someone will tell you &amp;quot;the number 12 is everywhere&amp;quot; and it will feel as if the number 12 is haunting you.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
you&#x27;ll see it everywhere- buses, milk cartons, the time.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
every turn of every corner of your day will find some cruel way to remind you of what you&#x27;ve lost.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
a photo, or an odd possession of theirs might be expected to stir up some feelings,&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
but it sneaks into where you least expect it.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
a song, a color, a face, a phrase that knocks the wind out of you as if the number 12 had learned muay thai.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
and all of the sudden you&#x27;re back at the start.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
where was i&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
where was i when it happened&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
what was i doing&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
what could i have done&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
why did she do it&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
why why why&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
maybe she&#x27;s happier now. maybe it truly was too much to bear.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
but what could it have been that she had to bear it alone?&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
the weight of the world was never meant just for her, why did she insist upon holding it?&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
we were all here.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
the world has been robbed of its kindness and its beauty.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
it seems shes taken it all with her&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
and left us.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
every memory, every moment, every photo is a reminder of how half of that story ends. how her story ended.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
to look at a childhood photo and know what the you then didnt.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
to know you&#x27;d be speaking at her funeral in 10 years.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
we were close back then, but we faded apart.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
when i got to high school we reconnected, and the kindness she extended towards me changed my life.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
it wasn&#x27;t huge, but it was unconditional. i didn&#x27;t even love myself unconditionally.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
even for a small moment, i got to experience the kindness she had grown into.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
we grew apart again when she went to college, which is fine. i don&#x27;t blame either of us for falling out of touch.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i wish i had texted just once.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i knew the depth of the person we were mourning that day. i understood it.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i felt a certain guilt being a speaker amongst her two best friends and her aunt, &lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
but every word of their loving recollections felt all too familiar for me to be a stranger.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
she saw people for who they really are&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
that one stuck in my head for the entire service.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
what a wonderful gift. &lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
to understand people. &lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
and at that to understand them more than theyd like you to.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
to understand who they are&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
not who they say they are&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
she certainly understood me for who i was&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
underneath all those layers of embarassingly baggy clothes&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
and embarassingly smudged eyeliner&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
she understood me&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i wish she knew how much that meant to me.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i wish i could tell her.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i love you so much&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
thank you for being you&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
you were always enough&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i dont know what i could&#x27;ve said to change her mind&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i dont think im qualified to even brainstorm&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
but i know i wish she didn&#x27;t&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
ive wished so hard; harder than i ever have, for longer than i ever have.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
its been days and weeks&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
and it will be months and years and decades of wishing and wishing&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
my 30&#x27;s and 40&#x27;s will come and go and &lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i will still be wishing that kind, sweet girl i grew up with was still around to talk&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
maybe by then i wouldve gotten to know her again&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
thats what stings the most&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i didnt know her&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i didnt know who shed grown into&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i knew her&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
thats it&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
now thats it&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i find myself mourning the amazing person she grew into&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
the amazing person that touched the lives of all three hundred people in that church&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
a feat im certain the 10 year old i was acquainted with was under-equipped for&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
no, no&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
she was so much more than i ever knew&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i find myself mourning the person i never got to know&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
it feels wrong&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
it feels dirty&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
like a trick has been played on me&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
a certain eventually has been taken without any warning&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
maybe it was my fault for it being an eventually&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
why wasn&#x27;t it just a now&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
maybe that check in wouldve done it&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
maybe she wouldve thought not tonight&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
maybe she wouldve been just distracted enough with our memories together&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i know just how distracting they are now&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
the worst part&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
and i mean the worst part&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
she doesnt know&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
she certainly didnt think about me in those last moments&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
or any of those other people in the church bar a few&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
she didnt picture me standing up there, &lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
shaking as i read a sorry substitue for the words i wish i had told her&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
she didnt picture the tears, the screams, the absent staring into space for weeks on end&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
of every single person in that room.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
yet here i am writing about it.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
crying through my fingers into my keyboard because tears wouldnt come close to enough.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
so many people cared so much about her.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i wish she had known; maybe things would be different.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i walked up onto the stand with my speech on my phone. &lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
ive never been a poor public speaker, but up there it all hit me&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
the gravity, the grief, the realness, it was all there in that church air&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
staring at me&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i started my speech.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
people laughed&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
people cried&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
as i approached the end, the emotion overtook me.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i couldnt do it&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
it was too much&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i couldnt accept it in front of everyone&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i didnt want it to be real&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i looked in her moms eyes&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
my aunt, as i called her&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i had been avoiding making eye contact. i had been a coward&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
the pain that she must have been going through is unimaginable&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i was afraid that even eye contact would make me burst into tears&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
but when i looked in her eyes&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
i saw so much love&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
for her daughter&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
that had been taken too soon from her&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
but it was love that was unpersuaded to let the footnote overtake the story&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
love that was unerased by grief&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
love that was unbothered by physical presence&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
love that saw her daughters presence in the lives of anyone who had been touched by her kindness.&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
love that told me to continue&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
to not let my grief stop me&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;span style=&quot;color: purple;&quot;&gt;i love you grace&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so i ask of you this&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
just as you extend it unto others&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
please&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
please&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
please&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
give yourself patience&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
give yourself kindness&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
give yourself compassion&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;
give yourself grace&lt;br&#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Lucas&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Terrifying Future</title>
        <published>2024-06-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-06-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Lucas Newcomb
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://pants721.github.io/blog/the-future/"/>
        <id>https://pants721.github.io/blog/the-future/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://pants721.github.io/blog/the-future/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I saw my life branching out before me like the green fig tree in the story. From the tip of every branch, like a fat purple fig, a wonderful future beckoned and winked... I saw myself sitting in the crotch of this fig tree, starving to death, just because I couldn&#x27;t make up my mind which of the figs I would choose. I wanted each and every one of them, but choosing one meant losing all the rest, and, as I sat there, unable to decide, the figs began to wrinkle and go black, and, one by one, they plopped to the ground at my feet.&amp;quot; &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sylvia Plath, The Bell Jar&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The summer before my senior year of high school has just begun, and this poem by Sylvia Plath has been ever-present in my mind. I am at the precipice of adulthood. I need to think seriously about my future and what I want to do, which is terrifying. For the longest time, I thought I had it figured out: &lt;em&gt;I am good at programming, I enjoy programming, and programming is interesting. I will go to college and become a programmer&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;, which felt like a great plan- what a great plan! But then I got back into being more politically conscious and back into Socialism. I got back into learning about what&#x27;s happening in Palestine right now (I am aware of the first-world irony of &amp;quot;getting back&amp;quot; into caring about mass genocide). I was left with a rotten feeling in my chest. This rotten feeling would become an overwhelming sickness whenever I sat down at my computer to work on a programming project or any Comp-Sci-related matter. I recognized this feeling- we had danced before. It was a feeling that visits me often in the late hours of the night as I lay alone and I, for some reason, decide to confront my mortality; a feeling that demanded that I read Camus and Nietzsche, a feeling that prompted me to enroll in a philosophy course to search for a solution to it. As I sat at my computer, staring at the colorful letters of my terminal, I was filled with existential dread. I would stare at the screen and think, &lt;em&gt;Why am I doing this? Why is this meaningful to me?&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;, which led me to question other things: &lt;em&gt;What&#x27;s meaningful to me? Why is this thing more meaningful than others? What does it mean for something to have meaning?&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is meaning?&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the next few weeks, I was thrown into an existential bender. I had been so sure of this plan for so long; is it possible that it could all be wrong? I&#x27;ve concluded that I feel this way about coding because of how I feel about capitalism. I associate capitalism with a lack of profound meaning. You work all day, every day, for your entire life to operate the business machine that benefits a small group of people who don&#x27;t even know you. Conversely, in a Socialist or Communist society, there is a sense that you are contributing to your community and bettering life for everyone. This is not to say that jobs that benefit one&#x27;s community don&#x27;t exist under capitalism. Still, they are rarer and more challenging to survive doing under capitalism than under an alternative economic system. Programming as a profession is especially a victim of this notion. There is seldom an idea of &amp;quot;pro-bono&amp;quot; programming or a programmer worker-owned co-op. Instead, programmers are seen almost as tools to corporations: replaceable, completely unspecific from their current company, and not in charge of any direction the company might go. To a capitalist, a programmer is an utterly internal tool- which doesn&#x27;t sit right with me. I consider myself somewhat gifted (I&#x27;m not an asshole, I swear), but not in the elementary school gifted kid way you might assume. While I am good at things that are usually academically valued, I am gifted because I was born into a high-income area with excellent access to education and the internet and two loving parents. This environment has allowed me to excel in programming and academic fields, as well as music, writing, and other creative fields. I have been given so many unique opportunities, resources, and abilities that I can use to cause good in this world, how can I possibly stomach being a nameless tool to an already wealthy capitalist? I can help other people and contribute to what I think is right. It matters to me that I fight the good fight. While I realize that it&#x27;s possible to contribute to social change outside of my career, I don&#x27;t think I can live with choosing a career that directly contradicts any contributions I make. I care about social change and the direction the world is headed, and corporate programming doesn&#x27;t align with either. This doesn&#x27;t mean that I can&#x27;t be a programmer, but it certainly thins the herd of programming jobs in which I will feel fulfilled by my career.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem is that while I care deeply about all this, the world does not. Regardless of how I navigate these feelings, soul-less jobs will stay lucrative, and meaningful jobs will remain underpaid. I can&#x27;t completely dismiss the possibility of taking a soul-less software job and finding meaning elsewhere because that might make me the happiest.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;codewithoutrules.com&#x2F;2019&#x2F;04&#x2F;12&#x2F;meaningful-programming-work&#x2F;&quot;&gt;This&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; post by Itamar Turner-Trauring makes some great points about this dilemma. One point that struck me is that there are programming jobs that are actually &lt;strong&gt;good&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;. Some companies are working to save the planet, and they need programmers. Working at a company like that would feel meaningful to me. The demands of environmental research are usually more engineering-focused, so I might also try to aim my future degree toward an engineering field.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe I could be an engineer; who knows? Engineering seems like a field I&#x27;d be well suited for. Still, I feel apprehensive about setting my sights on an engineering degree. For one, I&#x27;ve spent four years teaching myself how to code, so changing to engineering now would make me feel like it was all in vain. On top of that, I failed physics class. Okay, maybe I didn&#x27;t &lt;em&gt;fail&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;, but It was by far my lowest grade at a B+. And I didn&#x27;t get that B+ because I didn&#x27;t have what it takes- I&#x27;m really good at math, and I&#x27;m a good student. I got that B+ because physics was insanely boring to me. But can I really let one bad class set me back from pursuing something that might lead me to a lifetime of happiness? Is it so daunting to teach myself something from the ground up? I&#x27;ve done it again and again, why not one more? I could see the four years I&#x27;ve spent programming as a waste of time, or it could be four years of valuable experience in a technical field that can only help me in my future endeavors. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So maybe I&#x27;ll try engineering; maybe I won&#x27;t. This post could be a bunch of BS I&#x27;ll read someday with a pang of nostalgic disappointment in myself for succumbing to the money and safety of a cushy coding job. But who knows? I don&#x27;t.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The future is scary, and there are many different ways that people attempt to cope with it. I haven&#x27;t found my way yet, but maybe that&#x27;s okay. The future can be scary, but it won&#x27;t kill me (at least not while it&#x27;s happening). I can rest knowing that the future is my future, and my future is one where I will not settle for anything less than what feels right to me.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Lucas&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Pilot</title>
        <published>2024-03-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-03-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Lucas Newcomb
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://pants721.github.io/blog/pilot/"/>
        <id>https://pants721.github.io/blog/pilot/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://pants721.github.io/blog/pilot/">&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, welcome to my website. I&#x27;ve been meaning to make a website for a
long time, but I&#x27;ve always struggled with making something that&#x27;s both good
looking and functional as I&#x27;m not much of a frontend guy. Because of my general
lack of interest in the frontend world, I had no idea that static site 
generators (SSGs) existed, which make the entire process of creating a website
an order of magnitude easier.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I ended up doing some research into static site generators and found &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;pants721.github.io&#x2F;blog&#x2F;pilot&#x2F;jamstack.io&quot;&gt;Jamstack&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, 
which is a great resource for this type of stuff. Looking through the options 
on Jamstack, &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.getzola.org&quot;&gt;Zola&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; caught my eye as it&#x27;s written in 
Rust, and I am nothing if not a Rust shill. I later found out that using a 
SSG is completely independent of the language it is written in, but supporting 
Rust technology is always a win for me.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initially, Zola&#x27;s project structure was super confusing to me (and it still
is to an extent). There&#x27;s the basic stuff that most SSG&#x27;s share, like the 
directory for content, a config file, templates, and a theme, but Zola has some 
unique parts that were increasingly confusing for me. One of them was using
markdown as a form of configuration. Most SSG&#x27;s, like Hugo, for example, use 
some sort of configuration in their markdown files through the TOML &lt;code&gt;+++&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; 
section or the YAML &lt;code&gt;---&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; section, but Zola has mandatory markdown files that 
are (mostly) dedicated to just configuration through &lt;code&gt;_index.md&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; files. I still
don&#x27;t &lt;em&gt;really&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; understand it, but I understand it enough to get this site 
working. I understand that it configures the section or directory, that it&#x27;s
found in. For example, the &lt;code&gt;_index.md&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; file for the &lt;code&gt;&#x2F;blog&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; section on this site
looks like this:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;md&quot; style=&quot;background-color:#1a191a;color:#bebebe;&quot; class=&quot;language-md &quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-md&quot; data-lang=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;+++
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;+++
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, weird. Well, usually, it would hold some configuration that dictates what
templates the section and pages use, what the title is, etc. I suppose mine is
empty because of the &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;pants721&#x2F;no-style-please&quot;&gt;theme I&#x27;m using&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. 
I found this theme on Zola&#x27;s theme page, but I had a number of personal nitpicks
with it, so I just decided to create my own fork of it. As of right now, I have
a few things I need to change still:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Make the tab title read &lt;code&gt;Section :: MySite&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; instead of just &lt;code&gt;Section&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Make the dark mode not just a literal inverse of light mode&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once I settled on a theme, the development of this site was super easy. I just
had to fit it to the structure I wanted and then deploy it. As of the writing of
this post, this site is being deployed using &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;pages.github.com&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
and the continuous integration from my repo is being done by the very cool
&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;shalzz&#x2F;zola-deploy-action&quot;&gt;Zola deploy Github action&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. I&#x27;m
super happy with how this has all turned out, and I think I&#x27;ll be sticking with
this for a while.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are still things I want to implement on this site that I haven&#x27;t had the 
time to do today. Here&#x27;s a general list that I might come back to update&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Create an about page so I can talk about myself&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Maybe add some images&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Add a footer&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Add a projects tab&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Get some more stuff on the contact tab&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Add a devices tab&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
(long-term) Add CV&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The intended purpose of this site is mostly to write about stuff I like, which 
includes programming, computers, basketball, volleyball, philosophy, music,
and much, much more. I have quite a lot of interests, which I&#x27;m sure I&#x27;ll write 
about on my &amp;quot;about&amp;quot; page, and I think they will be a big part of this site as 
I&#x27;m still young enough to not need my website to be super professional. Another
purpose of this site is to inform prospective employers about my qualifications
and show that I am one of the few developers with the ability to read and write.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also want to use this as a place to document my academic writing. As of right now,
I&#x27;m a junior in high school, and I&#x27;m currently procrastinating working on my
IB Philosophy IA on &lt;em&gt;The Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. I don&#x27;t know if
I&#x27;ll publish that one as I&#x27;m not too optimistic about it, but I do want to publish
my IB Extended Essay comparing Camus&#x27; &lt;em&gt;The Myth of Sisyphus&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; and another TBA
philosophical writing about the nature of meaninglessness, and specifically how
we as humans should handle that.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#x27;s about it for the introduction to this site; thanks for reading.
To many more!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Lucas&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
