<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>pants-hub - la-haine</title>
    <subtitle>Lucas Newcomb&#x27;s personal site</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://pants721.github.io/tags/la-haine/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://pants721.github.io"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2024-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://pants721.github.io/tags/la-haine/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>La Haine - &quot;Jusqu&#x27;ici tout va bien&quot;</title>
        <published>2024-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Lucas Newcomb
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://pants721.github.io/blog/la-haine/"/>
        <id>https://pants721.github.io/blog/la-haine/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://pants721.github.io/blog/la-haine/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Heard about the guy who fell off a skyscraper? On his way down past each floor, he kept saying to reassure himself: So far so good... so far so good... so far so good. How you fall doesn&#x27;t matter. It&#x27;s how you land!” &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are certain movies that stick with you; &lt;em&gt;La Haine&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; is certainly one of 
them. Since I saw the movie for the first time last week, it hasn&#x27;t left my 
mind. &lt;em&gt;La Haine&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; is a movie that forces upon you the enviroment it portrays as 
it keeps the viewer in constant conflict. As we follow the three-color trio of 
Vinz, Sayid, and Hubert in their journey across Paris and it&#x27;s suburbs, we find
ourselves stumbling to find any sort of moral footing in the black and white 
world we&#x27;re confronted with. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This feeling is not only caused by the setting, 
but we are infected with it by the characters. Vinz struggles to reconcile the 
hard exterior he attempts to uphold with his deep-rooted empathy and humanity.
This conflict is only made worse when he finds the gun of a police officer, 
something uncommon in France and the 90&#x27;s. He feels a responsibility to take action against the polic who brutalized their now hospitalized peer Abdel. However, as their day goes on, doubt is sowed into Vinz&#x27;s mind as he begins to feel more and more that his actions would not be a catalyst for change, but merely a blip in the cycle of violence of a society in freefall. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This doubt is no better represented than in Hubert, the second in the trio. Throughout their journey, Hubert aims to deny Vinz the violence the reactionarily craves. Although Hubert feels the same anger for the brutality their peers are subjected to by the police, Hubert feels that violence will not solve anything. While Vinz demands action, Hubert is far more aware of his position in society. Vinz sees the projects as something to liberate, but Hubert sees them as a jail cell, preventing him from reaching the prosperity he desires. Hubert is his family&#x27;s main financial support, so he sells drugs to make ends meet.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trio of &lt;em&gt;La Haine&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; represent the actors in the cycle of the projects (in a deeper sense than literally). In this cycle where violent oppression is a given, there is the fighter, the product, and the victim. Vinz represents the fighter, as he aims for a violent retribution for the brutality the projects have faced. He fights every hour of the day, but cannot bring himself to kill- to fight in a way that&#x27;s permanent. Because of the unreset he&#x27;s made with the establishment, he is eventually killed accidentally by a police officer while being held at gunpoint. While Vinz is the fighter, he is still a victim. He is a victim of an enviroment with no clear way to fix things besides what&#x27;s been taught to them- violence. But the violence he&#x27;s taught is somewhat of a &lt;em&gt;playful&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; violence, and this is displayed in his aformentioned hesitation to kill and the accidental nature of his death. And it seems that the police in the movie share this playful understanding of violence as the cop is shocked when he kills Vinz, even laughing. Roughing eachother up, pointing guns, rioting, and brutalizing civilians; it&#x27;s fun until someone dies.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So who is the victim? The victim is Hubert. Hubert feels misplaced in the setting of the French ghetto. While Vinz and Sayid seem to be where they &amp;quot;belong&amp;quot;, there&#x27;s a lingering feeling that Hubert is meant for &amp;quot;better&amp;quot; things. He&#x27;s the only one who fits in well with the people they meet in Paris. However Hubert is not in Paris because he is the sorrowful victim of the cycle. Hubert is characterized by his pacifism throughout the film, but by the end of the film he points a gun at an officer. Hubert represents those who don&#x27;t wish to participate in the cycle of violence, but are nevertheless forced to. When the fighter has fought to hard and gets himself killed, Hubert, someone who never wanted violence in the first place, is forced to hold a gun to the police and have a gun held to him. But who is he a victim of? This is a central question of the film. While the obvious answer is that Hubert is a victim of the police and their brutality, the moral ambiguity of the projects seeps into my reasoning and makes me think of Vinz. Hubert would not have ended up in this situation without Vinz dragging him into it. Vinz hates the police, but his senseless violence and calousness is analogous to that of the police. This lends to the idea that Hubert is not the victim of Vinz or the police, but the victim of a river that the fighters and the police are too busy swimming in to let the current calm. And now, because the water has seeped into his home and he has dived in to save his friend, &lt;em&gt;Hubert must swim&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. However, the point is not against protest or retribution. The action of the fighter causes the bystander to become the victim, but the inactivity of the bystander causes the death of the fighter. Hubert has the gun aimed on the officer holding Vinz at gunpoint, unbeknownst to the officer; but he doesn&#x27;t pull the trigger and Vinz dies. While the situation is perpetrated by the fighters and the police, people will die regardless of the bystander&#x27;s inactivity.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cycle is reflected in the final moments of &lt;em&gt;La Haine&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. Hubert and the cop aim at eachother; a shot rings out; &lt;em&gt;black&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. We will never know who dies at the end, but it doesn&#x27;t matter and the mystery is meant to reflect this. Hubert still aims his gun at the cop and the cop moves his sights from Vinz to Hubert. The death of Vinz is meaninglessness as they&#x27;ve found themselves in the same situation regardless. The same will ring true for the death of the cop or the death of Hubert, as it did for Abdel and for Vinz. The cycle continues in it&#x27;s path, regardless of the role one might have in it; nothing changes. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
